- [Rough breathing]
- [♪ Meaningful music]
[Heavy breathing]
[Sniffling sound]
- [Woman’s surprised gasp]
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
[Tense sound effect]
[surprised gasp]
- [Rain of gunshots]
- [People screaming]
[shaking breathing]
[Woman's surprised gasp]
[bird chirping]
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
- [Tense sound effect]
[surprised gasp]
- [Rain of gunshots]
- [People screaming]
[shaking breathing]
[♪ Exciting music]
[camera shutter sound]
Issued as of March 13, 2024
Search and seizure of GR E&C
Let's proceed
[Noisy noise]
- [Knock knock]
- [♪ Music stops]
[Soryong’s sigh]
[knock knock]
How are you?
No, in front of Heo Geum-ran
It was completely flying.
[Jinwoo] When I was at the broadcasting station
- No matter how many times I wrote GR articles,
- [Soryong’s Sigh]
He didn’t even budge.
Because you only broadcast once
Immediate search and seizure [laughs]
[So-ryong] Reporter Hwang of Hanju Ilbo
Ah
You know, I'm capable...
Let's go, time's up
[Car starting sound]
[Limit] GR Broadcasting
[Small] I did it
You did it? you are?
[Jinwoo] I’ll call you
Xiaoryong, I'll call you.
[In-house lawyer] Just a moment
Sleep, wait, wait!
two minutes
You can't get excited
If you get excited about fighting the law
That's it
Well, I have a legal mind.
I'll handle it cleanly
What are you two
Just sit there with force
[In-house lawyer] No!
GR provided lobbying funds
Isn’t that a fact?
[GR Lawyer] The informant’s
You're talking about credibility.
- He's a thief who stole money.
- [♪ Interesting music]
That person reported it
How did you believe it and broadcast it?
[in-house lawyer banging] We
Did you just broadcast it with words?
- [Laughs]
- Are you laughing?
Image analysis results
Only the part where 100 million was stolen was cut off.
There is no other manipulation
It's true, there's no noise
How many times are we talking about this?
Ah, I'm really going crazy.
- [In-house lawyer’s frustrated words]
- Lawyer, lawyer, lawyer
- [So-ryong] Attorney Yeo Yun-cheol
- What?
[Rough breathing]
[Sound of putting it down]
The essence is
GR to avoid the Serious Disaster Act
Illegal funds have been mobilized
[Soryong] Because of that
numerous fatal accidents
It means that it has been concealed and reduced.
That was the core of our broadcast.
At the end of the broadcast
There was also a very short report video
As a result of the analysis, the problem related to false information is
With nothing at all
- It was finally confirmed.
- [♪ Interesting music]
How many times did I tell you?
Ten times what you just said.
[GR Lawyer] That
If you did it before the broadcast
It was good, ah
Oh, why are you putting so much effort into broadcasting?
- [Legal Team Leader, GR Attorney’s Laughter]
- [Beeping sound]
[So-ryong] The informant
I took a share in the middle
If you want to appeal
We are happy to report any counter-arguments.
How many times
Did I tell you?
[Sharp sound effect]
I don't see any intention to mediate.
Just do it by law.
That's right
After the broadcast, there was a report regarding GR.
You know it’s raining, right?
[So-ryong] Even on the day of the accident
To silence the bereaved family
I wrote a 200 million dollar agreement
You sent the proof right away.
- Uh, uh...
- [Limit] Huh?
Being built on the beach in Gyeongnam
Are ocean view apartments safe?
I'm thinking of stopping by next week.
The law is the law
The broadcast is as broadcast
- Let's proceed like that.
- [GR lawyer’s bewildered voice]
What is the law?
The Legal team will take care of it.
[So-Ryong] We didn’t suffer any damage
We'll broadcast it.
Uh, we…
[Soryong] Let’s go.
[GR Lawyer] Me, PD.
- PD, PD.
- [Sound of door opening]
- [Sound of door closing]
- [Embarrassed laughter]
The law is the law, the broadcast is the broadcast.
[laughter]
[Legal Team Leader, GR Attorney Sigh]
[So-ryong] So
Are you really going to do a follow-up broadcast of GR?
[Limit] Even before the results come out
I don't think there's any need to relax
I saw you filing a lawsuit.
[Soryong] What about Grimflower Kindergarten?
Did you remove it out of consideration?
Well, if you need a follow-up broadcast.
You can put it in
As the representative of the bereaved family, I give permission.
[Limit] As a producer, I will refuse.
I have so many pictures to write about.
[So-Ryong] I have a lot of drawings to write about.
Why are the viewership ratings so low?
[Limit] That’s it, the viewers
Corporate corruption in the first place, huh?
Well, labor issues and things like that.
Because I’m not interested.
Have you not seen the data analysis?
I'm 1% higher than average
It came out higher.
[So-Ryong] Author Hong is also right.
You can't broadcast by digging.
[Limit] Is it my money?
[Soryong] Even if I say it
[Hando’s sigh]
If this isn't done on public broadcasting,
Who does it?
[Hando] Okay, that’s enough, ah
[Card recognition sound]
[Guidance voice] The door is open
[Soryong] Let’s go together
[Tap sound]
- What are you doing?
- [♪ Interesting music]
[So Ryong] What?
- This
- [Soryong] What?
[Limit] No
Why do people like this
Tap, tap, tap, that's it?
when?
Please turn on your blinkers and come in.
[Button operation sound]
- [Sound of elevator doors opening]
- [Limit’s Sigh]
I've been waiting since morning
Thank you for your hard work!
- [Team Member 1] Thank you for your hard work.
- [Team Member 2 cheers]
[Daeyong] When you go to Lieutenant Commander
He only wore those clothes
Where to go to the outlet
Can you buy me some kadamai?
Move over, it's my place.
[Sound of bag falling]
[Daeyong] Oh, please put at least a chair.
I mean CP, all the time, huh?
[Team Member 3] Shall we order a chair?
[Daeyong] Yes, a big cushion.
[Team Member 3] Yes
[So-ryong] Who are you?
Ah, the newly selected youngest writer.
It's sweet and nice
This is Park Jin-mi, a real beauty.
I will work hard
- [Daeyong’s exclamation]
- [Embarrassed breathing]
- [Delicacy] Drink coffee
- Oh, I don't use disposable products.
[Surprise gasp] Next time
I'll prepare it in a mug
[Daeyong] Hey, as expected [Laughs]
- [Mobile phone operating sound]
- [Delicacy] Chair with plenty of cushions
[Daeyong] Oh, very good, uh
No, that level of energy
Will it last a week?
What about the author?
No, not yet
I was going to ask you
No, I wasn't told anything else.
[Daeyong] Oh, it’s just family.
It's just me and my mother
- What happened?
- [♪ Calm music]
[Thermometer operating sound]
[Writer Hong] Fish oil
I went to the hospital, but I still have a fever.
I'm fine
Mom, you can really go to work.
Hey
What kind of mother is boiling hot?
Are you leaving your daughter behind?
make money later
Only then will you know how your mother feels.
Grandma is coming later.
I'm really fine
Grandma is grandma
Mom is a mom, right?
[Writer Hong] Today
I'll be right next to you
We don't even have a grandfather
I don't even have a father
When three women come together
Any trials and difficulties
can overcome
You know you can't forget, right?
Ugh, nagging.
[laughter]
- [Author Hong’s playful sounds]
- [Author Hong’s daughter’s laughter]
The theme of this work is
The naivety of adolescent men and women...
[Teacher clears his throat] It’s love.
Well, first of all, if you look at the features
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Sound of surprise]
Teacher Nam
Ah, ah, sorry, I was just thinking about it.
- Oh, sorry.
- [Teacher 1] Coffee
thank you
[Male teacher sighs]
Last time I came
Is it because of that letter?
Yeah [sigh]
Is that why you're late in the morning?
I came out after an early morning swim.
the tire was torn
[Teacher 1] Huh?
[Male teacher] Call for insurance
I went to the car center
I think someone did that on purpose.
[sigh]
- Teacher Nam
- [Male teacher sighs]
[Teacher 1] Let’s report it first, okay?
Let's go have a delicious lunch.
- [Teacher 1] Let’s go
- [light laughter]
[Teacher 2] Shall we go out and eat today?
[Noisy noise from students]
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Sound of rustling paper unfolding]
[Male teacher’s trembling breathing]
- [Teacher] Teacher Nam
- [Rustling sound]
- What is that?
- [Male teacher] Oh, no. [Sigh]
[Teacher] Me
I was thinking about leaving work together.
Oh, I…
[Male teacher] I have an appointment
[Laughing awkwardly] See you tomorrow
[Teacher] Teacher Nam
[Police] So
Sentenced to life imprisonment 10 years ago
I went to prison
Suddenly a letter like this arrived
And I think this is what he did.
Is that correct?
[light sigh] Yes
[Police] Uh, for now
If you send a letter from prison
Like this on the envelope
There can be no sender
In the middle of the back and forth correspondence
They all test like this.
An anxious mind
I completely understand.
- First of all...
- [Male teacher] I, ah, I
As I said before,
The wheel on my car was torn this morning.
The person who repairs it
Someone ripped it on purpose...
[Police] Then search the CCTV
I have to catch him.
Yes?
[Police] If you escaped from prison
There must have been an uproar in the news already.
I heard you went to prison.
No, that person
I'm not a superpower
How can you go to prison to cut a tire?
- [Sounds around you become distant]
- [Sharp beep sound]
I saw you at the swimming pool!
in my ears
[screaming]
That song... [Crying sound]
[Crying sound]
[Male teacher] I’m sorry
[Police] Oh, um, um...
[Sound of door opening]
Well…
[Sound of door closing]
[Dog barking in the distance]
[♪ Meaningful music]
[sigh]
[Call connection tone]
Ah, yes, hello, driver.
[Sound of pulling out]
[So-ryong] Yes, I
Thank you, if you are using this
I'll return it to you as soon as possible.
Um, well, I don't know what was filmed.
- You won't have to worry.
- [Taxi driver’s response]
- Good night, thank you.
- [Taxi Driver] Yes
[Car remote control operation sound]
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[sigh]
[♪ Heartbreaking music
Yoo Jae-ha ‘Because I Love You’]
- ♪ The look in your eyes that I felt for the first time ♪
- [stretching sound effect]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
♪ Alone ♪
- [Man’s heavy breathing]
- ♪ Was it a misunderstanding ♪
[Male teacher’s surprised gasp]
[♪ Music stops]
[Man's sigh]
[Man] Are you happy, teacher?
[Male teacher’s trembling breathing]
- [Male teacher’s urgent breathing]
- [♪ Urgent music]
[Sound of surprise]
[Male teacher’s struggling voice]
[Sound of rustling things]
[Male teacher’s urgent voice]
[tire rubbing sound]
- [Car horn]
- [Tap sound]
[Male teacher] Oh, please save me!
Oh, save me... [Screaming scared]
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, author
[So-ryong] Teacher Nam?
- [♪ Calm music]
- [Sound of wind]
Author
[So-ryong] Ah, I
I received a call from author Hong.
This is PD Oh So-ryong.
Shall we go by car first?
- [♪ Calm music]
- [Crying sound]
[Male teacher sobbing]
[Small] Thank you
[Male teacher crying] I’m sorry
Hey, sorry
Because he forgot my number
How fortunate I am
[Sobbing]
- [Sound of locking]
- [Daeyong] Han PD
- [Car horn]
- Oh, what a surprise.
Why are you making the clank sound?
What is cornering, cornering?
You keep driving
If you're going to do it this way
Go eco-friendly like us
What the heck, I don’t even get CP
In a foreign car, this nigga
Oh, this is the shit car my dad drove.
how many times do i say this
[Symbol] But is CP also part of the group?
Did you guys have an emergency again?
[Small substitute] The police station
Did you do it for style?
Where are you bringing me?
The police said I ate it.
How many times do you say it?
- No, then take a shelter.
- [♪ Interesting and calming music]
The case must be reported to the police
It is possible to enter
Oh, then let’s go to the hotel.
[Daeyong] If something happens here
Who is responsible?
Ugly, ugly, really
Are you taking me to your house?
Why are you passing the blame on to others?
Veteran writer Hong?
It's not another crime, it's stalking.
Is that just stalking?
He is the one who deserted and committed terrorism.
[Writer Hong] But
Take her to a house where only women live?
I can't speak, Mr.
Oh, how do you know it's him?
What's going on at home?
Do you want to know?
[Writer Hong] Broadcasting station
Isn't this a national security facility?
As soon as 9 o'clock strikes tomorrow
To the prosecutor, that bastard
Until I found out he was in prison
It's as safe as here...
Ah, it's a national security facility in name only.
Well, even with a fire extinguisher
Me, huh? I can't move my pulse
[Daeyong] What national security facility?
- [Thump]
- Oh, surprise...
What, what, what?
A few days ago, I came to Mr. Nam.
It's a letter without a name
Just look at it, it’s that bastard
- [♪ Interesting music]
- What is it?
anti fingerprint
Haven’t you seen any movies or dramas?
[laughter]
Oh my gosh, I need to get my glasses fixed or something.
Honestly, right?
[Daeyong’s sigh]
I see you talking about the devil blah blah blah.
- [Daeyong] He’s not a sane guy.
- [Limit’s Sigh]
No, but that one too
You looked like you were out of your mind.
Just one chance
What if it's paranoia?
My headache hurts.
What kind of guy is Choi Ho-seong?
I'll find it and show you
Just wait
After seeing it, kick it out
Oh, it's so crazy, really.
[Male teacher] What if
What if I really saw it wrong?
So what should I do, writer?
The one who shot the arrow was a bad guy
secondary harm
Why did you do it yourself?
[Writer Hong] The wounds he received
Even if delusions arise
It was so terrible that it wasn't strange.
- After going through that terrible thing
- [♪ Calm music]
I lost my only grandmother and am alone...
- Whether it's been 1 year or 10 years
- [Male teacher crying]
You can get sick at any time
What if I saw something wrong?
You can go to the hospital and get counseling and treatment.
That's called mental illness
There is someone pointing a finger
I'm going to stick all my fingers
[laughter]
That time
If it weren't for the author...
[Soothing sound]
Mr. Eun-kyung
By the way, didn’t you change your name?
yes
Change your name too
I even changed my resident registration number...
Let’s eat hard, okay?
Even though they look like a ragtag bunch
We do quite a bit of work, we
I'm resting, I'll come back
- [Sound of door closing]
- [Deep sigh]
[sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes mom
[Writer Hong] Are you still working?
[Writer Hong] I don’t think I can go today
How is Jane?
[Writer Hong] My fever is fine and I’m snoring.
Make sure you sleep well at the door.
[Writer Hong] Yes, that’s right
- [Call end sound]
- [Knocking sound]
[Soryong] Author
[Sound of door closing]
M How is Sam?
[Writer Hong] Hmm
I know it's too much to ask, but
No matter how much I think about it
Find CCTV
I think I should report it to the police first.
I wonder if it’s really Choi Ho-seong
Honestly, I'm scared too, baby
Boy, I said that before I was alive
Someone who doesn't do it
[So-ryong] Why are you like that? Scary even to me
[♪ Meaningful music]
When it aired 10 years ago
Threatened to kill PD and me
I've received it countless times
[Writer Hong] But what should I do?
The law does not protect you
We should do it too
I risked my life to broadcast it.
[laughter]
How do we come back to square one after 10 years?
[Author Hong’s deep sigh]
yes
I'll take a look for now
[Siho] Wow, if it’s sincere reflection
Write it by hand or what is this?
Oh, what is it?
It's not the Korean version of Dennis Rader.
Right, bro?
[Hando] I don’t know who he is
No, you don't know that BTK killer?
'Bind', bind
'Torture', torture
‘Kill’, tight…
[Symbol] For 30 years
I killed ten people.
Why can't I catch you?
Keep sending letters
There's this idiot who kept mocking me.
In the end, I got caught up in it.
Although I went by accident
[light sigh]
[Tapping sound]
[Limit] How much more
Do I have to wait? [sigh]
- Until dawn for non-work matters...
- [Sound of door opening]
- [Sound of door closing]
-There is something called Poomat.
[Soryong] Friendly neighbors
The beautiful custom of helping each other
To author Hong
I didn't get any help
You did GR alone, right?
- I took the lead on that...
- [Daeyong] Ah, hey, it’s loud.
What is that?
- It's a video of Choi Ho-seong's crime 10 years ago.
- [clattering sound]
I was called out at this time
I know you're angry, but
[So-ryong] I hate being indebted to you
Writer Hong
- This is my first request.
- [Screen touch sound]
Let's see, okay?
[Host in the video] Entrance of the bride and groom
- [♪ Wedding march plays]
- [Applause and cheers from people in the video]
- [Camera shutter sound]
- [People applauding and cheering]
[Tense sound effect]
[clunk clank]
- [Emphasized sound effect]
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
[Hosung] Teacher
How can you leave me and meet someone else?
[emphasized footsteps]
[Shouting] Teacher!
[Male teacher’s surprised gasp]
[♪ Soaring music]
[Sounds around become quiet]
[emphasized clanging sound]
[Sound of reloading]
- [Rain of gunshots]
- [People screaming]
[♪ Nervous music]
[The gunfire stops]
[The sound of two people breathing hard]
Mr. Eun-kyung
[Heavy breathing]
[Male teacher’s surprised gasp]
[screaming]
[howling sound]
[Male teacher] Dongjae!
- Oh, no!
- [Sound of approaching footsteps]
[howling sound]
[surprised gasp]
[sigh]
[shaking breathing]
[♪ Heartbreaking piano performance
Yoo Jae-ha ‘Because I Love You’]
[Hosung] Now it’s just the two of us left
teacher
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Police in video] Ho-seong Choi! Raise your hands!
[Video sound stops]
[Daeyong] This is perfect
You're not crazy, is this?
fish oil, cow, fish oil, goosebumps, seed
[sigh]
[So-ryong] ‘1, the defendant surrendered himself.
'I am deeply reflecting'
'2, the victim is alive and
'There was only one death'
'3, Stalking is childish
It was an expression of pure emotion.'
'4, the defendant competed in various competitions.
'Suspicious'
‘A promising young man’…
Is this the verdict?
[Symbol] No, but even things like this
I just made it like this
If you get 30 years with this
Isn't this really something?
My grandfather is a military general.
[So-ryong] They say he comes from an elite family that has been passed down from generation to generation.
[Sigh of the sign]
Hey, what if this wasn't broadcast?
Life imprisonment would have been out of the question.
Until the trial, I was completely on the side of the perpetrator.
I'm sorry to the victim.
I'm taking my hands off
- [♪ Heavy music]
- [Soryong] What?
Are you sure you saw it all straight?
Already has a murder record
He's crazy.
without police
It's not our place to step forward.
[Hando] Even in the Garden of Faith
I attacked it blindly
Don't you remember that I almost died?
I guess he was a producer when he was a cat.
Let's borrow the help of that damn police officer.
We're going to step up now.
Because they don’t believe me
[Soryong] That’s done
What about you two?
[Symbol] Ah, yes, that
But now I
I'm too busy doing my own thing...
[Daeyong] Well, find the prosecutor in the morning
How are you doing in prison?
Let's check, first.
Let's say you're looking for it at 9 o'clock.
The prosecutor will cooperate
Is there any guarantee?
[So-ryong] In the meantime, just in case
That idiot
What if I find it here?
It might not be Choi Ho-seong.
[Thumping the table] That’s right!
If you check the CCTV, you will get the answer.
Why are you so anxious?
Are you waiting until morning?
[So-ryong] Finding evidence
First report it to the police
From the minimum safety
I'm talking about securing it, now.
So
That cumbersome and dangerous thing
Why do we do it?
It's not like I'm going to broadcast it right away.
[Soryong] Right?
I'm done with broadcasting.
[Hando’s sigh]
Okay
I'll do it alone
Oh, that…
Come home, everyone.
[Daeyong] Oh, me, oh, the team leader, that
I told the informants I knew
What prison is Ho-seong Choi in?
- [Symbol] Team leader, team leader
- [Daeyong] Team leader Oh, Team leader Oh
[Symbol] No, speak up, Mr.
[sigh]
[Sound of door closing]
- [Mobile phone operation sound]
- [♪ Nervous music]
"Republic of Korea Army"
[camera shutter sound]
[Soryong] Hello
Could it be that the underground parking lot was last night?
Can I see the CCTV?
No way
Oh, I have to have that.
Even if you ask the police for personal protection
Because I can do it
Even if the police come
If it can't be done, it can't be done.
[Security] Yes? Hey, go, go
Take this too
- Ah, ah, ah, eat this.
- [Guard] Come on, come on.
[Sound of elevator doors closing]
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Tense sound effect]
[Sound of door closing]
- [urgent sound]
- [Car horn]
[Male teacher’s terrified voice]
[Male teacher’s urgent voice]
[sigh]
[♪ Nervous music]
[Man's heavy breathing]
[Man's light laughter]
[♪ Music stops]
[Car remote control operation sound]
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Hando] What are you doing?
- [Soryong’s Scream]
- [Hando screams] Oh, why!
Ah, what are you doing, PD Han!
ah…
The security guard above
That's why I came here
[Soryong’s Lament]
Ah, well, I said I would take my hand off.
Ah, we absolutely
I heard you go as a team.
[Limit] ‘Trigger PD
'He was found dead while walking alone'
- [Sigh]
- I'm afraid an article like that will appear.
I just changed my clothes and came here.
I said I came because I was worried.
I do it in detail
I heard you closed the CCTV.
[sigh]
It's not like I have no income at all.
[♪ Interesting music]
Are you a detective?
Oh well, in 10 years of trigger
If I can't do this much, I'll die.
[Limit] Ha…
Let's just leave the car here.
That you are in control
To make you mistaken
Let's set a trap, make a mistake
No, this is evidence of a crime.
To go in droves
at least once
I'm not coming back
Why is it like that
Are you thinking all useful thoughts?
BTK killer, don’t you know?
Dennis, ah, there is, well, that…
- Put it back on?
- [Soryong] Paste it
here
- Here?
- [Soryong] Uh
[Limit] Do I really have to come this far?
[Soryong] Because I failed at the officetel
It didn't come
[Limit] So in the first place
If you haven't started yet...
[Soryong] Ah! nagging
If you're going to keep nagging me, why don't you just leave?
Why are you following me around, puppy?
[Limit] Tires here too
I can't secure CCTV for the puncture...
[So-ryong] Oh, really!
Do it tsk tsk tsk!
unluckily
[Limit] When will tsk tsk become the enemy? ttt tsk tsk
What are you doing, not going in?
There are days like that when reporting.
If you get hit once
I keep eating at a fast pace
[Hando’s frustrated sigh]
[Soryong] Oh!
Rather than you being picky
Still, I have a better impression
go to the car and wait
Hey, hello
[Limit] That’s me
[Sound of door closing]
[yawn]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of zipper being lifted]
[♪ Interesting music]
- [♪ Joyful music]
- Oh, wow, I can see it right here.
Wouldn't it be okay to just look at it for a moment?
[Employee] Yes, no.
Ah, our CCTV records are
I need to get approval from the managing director.
But you've been on vacation since yesterday
He's coming in a week.
Are you coming with the person in person at that time?
No way, here too
Is it okay for the police to come?
of course!
If you show me something like this
For no reason are our members excluded.
- No loss of members
- [Employee] No
- I'll just watch for 5 minutes, 5 minutes...
- You can't come in here.
- [Soryong] Yes
Oh, really
Just show me for a moment.
Not for a moment, not for a second.
- I'm leaving.
- [So Ryong] Really sleep...
[Employee] When you say something nice
I'm going out
- Yes, yes.
- [Employee] Yes
I'll go this way.
I'll open the door
- Yes, good luck, yes.
- [Employee] Goodbye
A little bit
- [So-ryong] One PD?
- [♪ Interesting music]
[Employee] Welcome
Are you looking for something?
[Clears cough]
[Limit] You’re only selling stuff, right?
the man from here
I heard you were leaving with your pants up?
Are you a police officer?
Do you look like a police officer?
[Laughs] What is it?
True
[Clears cough]
[Hando’s sigh]
What is this?
What should I do?
Tree…
[Hando] Right in front of me, ugh
CCTV footage projected in front of you
please show me that
Oh, CCTV footage?
Hey, me again
[Employee] Wait a minute, this is, ah…
Ah, here it is
here
Hey, it came out great, right? [snort]
If you don't want to buy it, go
[Employee clears his throat]
[Limit] Hmm
Show me and I'll buy it
The most expensive one here
Oh my, were you a customer? Wow
Would you like me to show you how many days it will take?
- [So-ryong] Uh, stop here.
- [Employee response]
[Keyboard operation sound]
Yes, but at this level
Even if the picture quality is improved
It might be difficult to see the face
Well, overcome the difficulties on your own.
[Employee] Now, this is the original file.
This USB
Service!
Now
[Employee laughter]
[Employee's strong breathing]
Now, your eyes are sparkling, your ears are pricked
Now, let me pay attention.
This is just a bit awkward to do.
Yes, just a moment [stressing sound]
- [♪ Lively music flows]
- Um
From now on, to the two of you
Products to introduce
Play gold right away
- It will be a VIP restraint set.
- [Sparkling sound effect]
It's so bright, right?
Top quality Italian leather
Luxurious box packaging
Above all, comfortable fit and
With a strong binding force
Satisfaction of sadism and excitement of masochism
These two rabbits
It means you can catch it.
That you could become a rabbit
Please keep in mind
Well, it's really simple to use.
Please tie me earnestly
earnestly
- [Slap] Please hit me.
- [Hando’s moans]
If you just feel it
There is a shortcut to Hong Kong.
Now, if you buy it right now
We will serve you under exceptional conditions.
Did you say you were going to buy this?
How much is it?
- ah!
- [So-ryong] 100,000 won?
Oh, wait, wait, wait
[♪ Music stops]
Wow, I almost made a double joke.
- [Employee] One million won.
- [Humorous sound effects]
Oh, I'm Trigger PD.
Oh, okay
20% discount to 80
Wow, what is this, compared to the price?
It’s a product that is very poor in cost-effectiveness…
[Limit] Lump sum payment
Lump sum payment?
Thank you, Ayu
Wow, you have a good person [laughter]
- Oh, wait a minute, do you have iron poison?
- [Limit] No
[Employee] Uh, okay, okay, okay.
- Okay, here’s the lump sum payment.
- [Hando’s whispering sound]
But who is S and who is M?
[Employee laughter]
[Hando's tired breathing]
That law
Where did you get it?
I didn't steal it.
When the owner dispatches his faithful dog,
Looks like they even gave it to me
[sigh]
[Hando] What are you doing?
The blinker is on
[Soryong] Nice
That's how the superiors spend their money.
Well done
Well done, Handdol
disability
[Hando] Well, she’s an unknown woman.
[Noisy sound]
Maybe
M What’s going on with you teacher?
ah…
Teacher Nam told you that…
Didn't you mention the letter?
No, what?
[Embarrassed breathing]
Well, don't tell me
I tried not to do it if possible.
Just keep your mouth shut about this
I don't think so
[Teacher] A while ago
An anonymous letter is addressed to Mr. Nam.
Did you get one?
- [Mocha] Is the team leader here?
- [Soryong] Good morning
- [Producer Yoon] Oh, are you here?
- [So Ryong] Good morning, good morning
[♪ Interesting music]
Oh, you got a new chair?
[Daeyong] They said they got CCTV footage
What about reporting?
[Soryong] I'm on my way back.
What happened to the prosecutor's side?
[Daeyong] Luckily
I found the prosecutor in charge.
Choi Ho-seong’s prison status is
They say you have to contact Teacher Nam directly.
[Soryong] Chi
[Daeyong] In order to protect human rights
Never tell a third party
Haze disease
[Symbol] Ayu, in Korea
Very perpetrator human rights are the best
If you want to be protected
You have to be a very abusive person
What about writer Hong and Nam Sam?
- [Scraping sound]
- [Writer Hong] Baby
Are you going to die?
I stopped singing and lost my smile.
Are you just going to die like that?
Eat to gain strength
You have to have strength to fight
Choi Ho-seong or anyone else
There's something I didn't say, author.
What?
I found someone I love
- I decided to get married.
- [♪ Calm music]
Maybe it started again
Is it because of that?
I'm so scared
[Male teacher] Could it be because of me?
Someone I love again...
[Crying breathing]
Does that person know about Choi Ho-seong?
male teacher
Call him right now, right now
[Writer Hong] Explain the whole situation
Just in case, call the police
Please at least request personal protection.
If you can't do it, I'll do it
Give me the phone
- No, no!
- [Grabbing sound]
[Male teacher] Ah, ah, no, I
I told you to break up with me on the phone yesterday.
We broke up
It's okay because it's over with me, right?
No, ah, if I contact you again
He found out again...
[Male teacher’s heavy breathing]
- [Author Hong’s sigh]
- [Sobbing]
[deep sigh]
[Author Hong’s exhale]
[Author Hong’s frustrated breathing]
[Soryong] Author
Why?
[Author Hong’s sigh]
What's going on?
- Teacher Nam
- [♪ Heavy music]
They said they found someone they love
[Writer Hong] Even promised marriage
What is normal now
A state that can be judged
I know it's not
[frustrated sigh]
Just, just everything
At least I
I should be on Mr. Nam’s side.
Over and over again
What makes me frustrated is that I…
me to me
I'm so angry, Team Leader Oh.
[Soryong’s Sigh] Author
It can be
The writer and Nam Sam too
no
It's not like that.
What a terrible time Teacher Nam had.
Did you endure it and come this far?
[Writer Hong] Right next to it
Watch and watch
[Crying] From my heart
It's like a sweet potato
So why did we start loving again?
[Sigh] You can’t do that.
It keeps coming up
[Author Hong’s sobbing breathing]
[Soryong’s sigh]
Why?
- [Male Teacher] Author
- [Writer Hong] What's going on?
- [shaking breathing]
- [Author Hong, Soryong’s surprised voice]
Why, what's going on?
Choi Ho-seong
He said he's not in prison right now.
[Male teacher’s crying and breathing sound]
[Author Hong’s surprised voice]
[♪ Sweet piano performance
Franz Liszt 'Dream of Love']
[bird chirping]
[♪ Continued piano playing sound]
[Sound of door closing]
[Daeyong] Suspension of sentence?
Hey, this guy is good too.
Oh, what happened, what on earth?
Well, one by one we
I think it would be difficult to handle it all
M To Attorney Sam
I asked you a favor.
Where did you find a lawyer?
[Knocking sound]
[Yuncheol] Hello!
- [♪ Humorous music]
- [Sound of door closing]
[Comically] This is lawyer Yeo Yun-cheol.
Yeo Yun-cheol, CEO of Law Research Institute
Female lawyer
[Yun Cheol] The in-house lawyer is
You know it’s a concurrent job, right?
According to the prosecutor's explanation,
Sseu-eup, imprisoned in prison
In less than two years
- He said he had a mental problem.
- [♪ Meaningful music]
Like a person possessed by a ghost
I became this person, then I became that person.
[Yuncheol’s laughter]
Well, as long as you don’t harm others
There haven't been any problems so far.
Write it
Is it from last year?
- It suddenly became violent, and people
- [Inmate's angry voice]
With a delusion that never existed before
While showing signs of hallucination
- Breaking the prison guard's arm
- [Noisy]
He almost killed another inmate.
[Medical device operation sound]
External test results
finally
Dissociative identity disorder appeared.
It's called multiple personality.
[Daeyong] I-C, just by listening to it,
This is old, this is
[Yuncheol] Anyway,
My sentence was suspended for interrogation.
I was admitted to an outside hospital three months ago.
Current status
Well, I mean hospitalization.
24 hours in a protective ward
Because we are being closely monitored.
Things like going out
They say it can't happen, yeah
[Author Hong] The victim notification system is
Did you do it for style?
[Tap] I said it a long time ago
You should have done it!
[Yuncheol] Oh, well, what
As it is the work of the country
Well, that’s right [laughter]
Ho-Seong Choi at the hospital
What is the possibility that he went out secretly?
[Yuncheol] Oh
That's okay though
I also checked with the police.
This has a card key sensor attached.
You have to go through the triple doors
It's a structure that allows you to go outside.
This card key has
I have the serial number.
When did you come and go, and who did you come in and out?
Everything is recorded automatically
Sneaking out is
Even normal people like us
They say it's impossible [laughter]
I checked the entry and exit records from the prosecutor's office.
They say there’s no problem with that either.
[Soryong’s sigh]
[after exhaling]
Guys, who am I?
I
Just ask the police for a favor.
Today’s photo of Choi Ho-seong
We got it, folks!
- [Yuncheol’s laughter]
- [♪ Heavy music]
Uh, that, that, that is confidential.
If you go outside
I'm going crazy, team leader.
[Soryong] What is this?
[limit] definitely
Does it look like someone else?
This guy and that guy have different impressions.
Aren't you an accomplice?
To be a complete stranger
What you’re doing is too ho-ho-seong.
[So-ryong] We reported it to the police.
The criminal's face in the CCTV is
When exactly will it come out?
[Yuncheol] What
There are so many incidents.
Ah, but oh team leader
CCTV that was a godsend
Thanks to that, I and Teacher Nam
Protect the safety of both your fiancés
It starts today.
[Writer Hong] Even if I die
I said I'm not going to my fiancé's house.
However, a person who is single by blood
Just trust the police
I can't send you home alone
[Daeyong] No, if you are that affectionate
Whether you take it to your own home...
It won't work
What about my house?
Are you serious?
[So-ryong] Well, no family, no kids.
My dad is home
It's almost like an empty house.
M If it’s okay with Sam, then what?
I don't care
Oh team leader
Will you tell me everything later?
First of all, I have Choi Ho-seong.
In search of a mental hospital
Is it okay to broadcast?
I'll figure it out and go
Until then
M Please stay with Sam for a while.
[Hando] What are you doing?
What is this box? The leather looks good
- Have you opened it?
- [Producer Yoon] No
[Symbol] What do you think you know?
- [Producer Yoon] It’s not.
- [Symbol] That’s right.
- [Producer Yoon] No
- [Symbol] What is this?
[Limit] Write, hand
-Why?
- [♪ Interesting music]
No, well, I'm going to trade in used goods anyway.
If either of you needs it
I'll give it to you at an unprecedented price.
[Limit] White Day limited
cash price
[Symbol] Ah, today is White Day
March 14th
[Producer Yoon] Yes, White Day
Shall we look at the items first?
- [♪ Interesting music]
- Both eyes sparkle, both ears perk up
[Limit] From now on
Products to introduce to you two
gold play
VIP
You have been arrested
[Producer Yoon] Who?
Above all, comfortable fit
So the two of you
If we tie each other up and hit each other
Being a rabbit
[Symbol] Tied up and beaten
How could a rabbit...
- Is it good?
- [Symbol] Is it good?
[Limit] Hong Kong
[Symbol] Hong…
[Producer Yoon] Ah
Oh, just look, oh
- [Clicking sound of opening]
- [Sparkling sound effect]
[♪ Soaring music]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Limit] 90, 95
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Button operation sound]
Are you using your Dharma well?
[Former President] Cha Seong-wook’s coverage
There is no progress
Or have you changed your mind?
I'm going to talk about it now though
I was going up
I'm looking forward to it
- [panting sound]
- [Rustling sound]
[♪ dark music]
[gurgling sound]
[panting sound]
[Chanting] Huh?
[In a trembling voice] When you pee,
I told you I was going to get scolded.
You're really getting scolded
Dudu I peed!
[Crying sound]
[shaking breathing]
Why are you sleeping already? uh?
I brought you something fun
[shaking breathing]
[clattering sound]
[Sound of refrigerator door closing]
[Excited breathing]
[So-ryong] Oh, wait a minute.
[Security] It’s an order from above.
How many times will I tell you
- No contact with the media!
- [So-Ryong] Ai, Ai!
Where on earth is it?
Since Ho-seong Choi came in, we have also
I'm just dying from so much pain
- How tricky.
- [Soryong] Who?
Who is so picky?
That's right...
Ah, go!
- [Soryong] Hey, wait a minute.
- [Security] Uh-huh!
Tsk
[Guard's sigh]
[The security guard's disapproving voice]
Uh, writer Jiyoon
[So-ryong] Why are you alone?
[Jiyoon] All PDs work outside the office.
Is it because it's White Day?
Everyone quit their job
Who is the new youngest?
Oh, him
Did you know I quit after one day?
- Trigger new record
- [Soryong] Huh
[Jiyoon] This is
It's not some kind of protection center.
why do we
Do we even have to provide victim care?
I even received a complaint text, I
[laughter]
Write, what should I say?
The world is getting weirder
I think it's getting tricky
- Regretfully
- [telephone ringing sound]
Yes, this is an investigative reporting trigger.
Uh, okay, just a moment.
- Team leader
- [So-ryong] Yes
I heard your fiancé is downstairs?
[Teacher] I’m sorry
You came here suddenly like this
Even if I ask you to tell me where it is
I'm silent.
But if you force yourself to find it,
I'm afraid it'll be harder
So instead of me
Please pass this along, PD.
[Soryong] Ah…
To Ga-yeon
The police and I will definitely protect you.
Please tell me this too
[Teacher] Please
Yes, I will.
A moment?
[So-ryong] Why did PD Han go in there?
[Hando] Team leader
-Are you okay?
- [Soryong] Huh?
I'm fine
[Limit] No
PD Kang said he had a job.
- Now, team leader…
- [So Ryong] What happened?
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
- [Limit] I don’t know.
[Soryong’s worried voice]
- [So-ryong] Why are the lights off?
- [Sound of a mobile phone being taken out]
[Door lock operation sound]
[Door lock operating sound]
[Voice guidance] Opened
- [Symbol] Happy birthday…
- [♪ Music stops]
[Both sigh]
[Tap] Look
Oh, the team leader is going to hate it.
[Soryong] Ahyu
Let's do this in this situation
To one PD…
Oh, otherwise that brother
I don't think he'll come, so...
- I should just stab him.
- [Elevator arrival sound]
[Daeyong] I guess this is enough, right?
Well, if it’s not enough, just order more…
Oh, well, what are you doing?
[Writer Hong] What is it?
[Daeyong] Ah, this…
There are only women in Baeksongi.
I said I was worried so I said let’s go…
[Songi] No
CP said it when he came.
I'm worried
[Daeyong] Hey, what is that?
What cake? Whose birthday is it?
[Symbol] Yes, March 14th
White Day is
Team leader’s birthday…
[Symbol] Character
No, we still gathered like this
The candle burns once
[Writer Hong] No Sugar Cake
- [Symbol] Ah, no sugar cake, it’s good
- [Daeyong’s laughter]
[♪ Calm music]
Thank you, Kiho Kang
[Symbol] Ah, what am I?
[Naughty sounds of symbols]
[Daeyong] Oh my, oh my
Oh my, oh my
[Soryong] Above all
M I’m worried about Sam and us.
For the first time in a million years
Our CP Dae-yong Park who brought out the gag.
[Symbol] Ha, that’s really ridiculous.
Applause!
[Daeyong’s awkward noise]
[Soryong] Thanks to you, I’m like this
We all eat together.
Oh, that's right
What is living like?
Is it this difficult to eat a meal?
So, I say bitch often...
- [Daeyong] Sseu-eup
- [Symbol] Even if you don’t use it
Even if you don’t use it, just do it
With each other in our hearts
Since you take care of me, I can endure it.
[Laughing] Well, this is it.
[So-ryong] Thanks to Nam Sam
first time at home
I tried all kinds of fresh green onions.
For a long time
Is it because I had no family?
It's like a real family
[Male teacher] It’s nice to see, really.
Me too
[Writer Hong] Drawing a line
You are our family too
PD Kang here
Older than one PD
[Soryong] You
those eyes
I saw it when I first parachuted.
It's not the look in your eyes
[Daeyong] Parachute?
[Symbol] Huh?
- [Limit] Turn off
- [♪ Music stops]
- [Daeyong] Turn it off…
- [So-ryong] Get out?
[Daeyong] Where…
- [Soryong] Ah, seconds
- [♪ Calm music]
- [Song-i laughs] Oh, it’s a surprise.
- [Symbol] Oh, I almost went out.
- [Writer Hong] Oh, I almost got angry
- [Daeyong’s laughter]
Now, let's all blow together.
one, two, three
[Each person blowing after blowing]
- [Sniffling sound]
- [Knocking sound]
[Male teacher] Yes
Ah…
[Soryong] Weren’t you uncomfortable?
Oh, yes, not at all.
[So-ryong] Ah, this
The person I love
M Please be sure to tell this to Sam.
[light laughter]
For a long time to come
Let's live with a smile, let's live
[♪ Calm music]
[light laughter]
yes
[Daeyong] No, just one rattle watch
Will it be protected?
It's later than it's close
Any one of you two
Just stand guard for one day
[Symbol] Oh, I’m sorry.
But I really have a lot of work to do.
- [Siho's laughter]
- [Tap sound]
[Daeyong] What about PD Han? Are you busy these days?
[Siho] Hey, I’m not busy.
[Daeyong] Ah, I will come tomorrow
Are you done?
[So-ryong] Oh, it’s okay.
Everyone is a burden, burden.
[Daeyong] Don’t be fussy
in commemoration
Take a picture and dig it up, quickly.
[So-ryong] What kind of photo is this? It’s tacky.
[Author Hong] Main book…
- [So Ryong] Come in.
- [Author Hong’s disapproving sigh]
- [Substitute] One, two
- [♪ Calm music]
- three
- [Camera shutter sound]
[So-ryong] Yes, please go in.
- [Daeyong] I'll go
- [Songi] Goodbye
- [Soryong] Uh, Baeksongi
- [Songi] Yes?
I stayed up all night looking for Choi Ho-seong’s data.
I'm saying that because I need to see it.
This is Seongwook’s father’s house.
It's a black box nearby.
[So-ryong] I wonder if the person who wrote the graffiti was caught?
Please check by tomorrow morning
- Okay.
- [Soryong taps] Yes, go in.
[Songi] Goodbye
- [So Dragon] Kang Ki-ho
- [Symbol] Yes?
- Give me a ride.
- [Symbol] Ah, yes
- Let's go, I'll go.
- [Songi] Yes
[Car starting sound]
[Soryong] Let’s go in.
Is it delicious, alone?
Just kidding
It's a birthday present.
[Soryong laughs]
[So-ryong] Aren’t you going to get off?
I want to confess
What?
what?
I'm Dr. Trigger
[♪ Calm music
blah 'Happening']
[Attorney Choi speaks softly] Oh my.
Thanks, mom. I'll work.
[sigh]
[Sound of intake of breath]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
- [Disapproving sound]
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
[Grumping sound]
[sigh]
Oh no
[♪ Rhythmically heightened music]
What is it?
It’s all different, really.
[Attorney Choi’s laughter]
[♪ ‘Happening’ continues]